ladies and gentlemen you've heard all
the evidence I submit that this was not
a Hot Blooded Crime of Passion consider
this a revolver holds Six Bullets not
eight that means that he fired the gun
empty and then stop to reload by the
power vested in Me by the state of Maine
I hereby order you to serve two life
sentences back to back one for each of
your victims so
be
[Music]
they send you here for life that's
exactly what they
take I believe in two things discipline
help
me and the
Bible here you'll receive both Andy came
to sha shank prison in
1947 why'd you do it I didn't since you
asked you going to fit right in I must
admit I didn't think much of Andy first
time my laid eyes on him he had a quiet
way about him a walk and a talk that
just wasn't normal around here there are
places in the world that aren't made out
of
stone there's something inside they
can't touch what you talking about Hope
let me tell you something my friend hope
is a dangerous
thing damn it new friend you're putting
me behind hope can grab a man
insane you better be sick or dead in
there I kid you
not better get used to that idea oh my
holy
God I guess it comes down to a simple
Choice
really get busy
living you get busy
[Music]
dying get busy
living or get busy
dying that's damn
right
[Music]
[Applause]
see